https://www.shannon-cpas.com/privacy/

Skip to content
Our Privacy Statement
Certified public accountants, like all providers of personal financial and accounting services, are now required by law to inform their clients of their policies regarding privacy of client information. CPAs have been and continue to be bound by professional standards of confidentiality that are even more stringent than those required by law. Therefore, our accounting firm has always protected your right to privacy, but we post this notice here to comply.
Types of nonpublic personal information we collect
We collect nonpublic personal information about you that is provided to us by you or obtained by us with your authorization.
Parties to whom we disclose information
For current and former clients, we do not disclose any nonpublic personal information obtained in the course of our practice except as required or permitted by law. Permitted disclosures include providing information to our employees and—in limited situations–to unrelated third parties who need to know that information to assist us in providing financial services to you. In all such situations, we stress the confidential nature of information being shared.
How we protect the confidentiality and security of client information
We retain records relating to professional services that we provide so that we’re better able to assist you with your professional guidelines. In order to guard your nonpublic personal information, we maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with our professional standards.
Please call if you have any questions, because your privacy, our professional ethics, and the ability to provide you with quality financial services are very important to us.
